[Music]
Prudential Cambodia life Assurance PLC a
second consecutive year recipient
the organization makes employees feel at
ease by assisting employees who require
assistance
hello from Prudential on behalf of
potential Cambodia family I am very
excited and thrilled to receive this
award best company to work for in 2022
despite the challenging year we have
gone through a lot with our colleagues
in the company we wrote out a lot of
initiatives
and all of these are anchored to four
key things Financial mental social
and physical well-being
and that is meant to help our colleagues
connect across the company
I'd like to name a few key initiatives
that make a picking pack on our
colleagues life we've introduced hybrid
working Arrangements where everyone is
no longer to come to office at 8 30 in
the morning and they've always surprised
because we believe that everyone has
different priorities second we wrote out
the in the first and leading women
enhancement agility which is longer
maternity leave they have longer time to
take care of the loved one third
each and everyone in the company is
eligible to invest and participate in
the future of the company they can
purchase potential shares and every two
shares that they purchase the company
top up one for free
there are a lot more initiatives that
help connect our colleagues across the
company we wrote out a new way of
working introduce our job we are working
where everyone can form support and
thrive
to work on a significant project that
made a big impact on our customers
employees and the society at Large
so in 2023 our commitment to our
colleagues Remains the Same which is to
help our police get the most out of life
and potential I am looking forward to
working with my colleagues in 2023 and
make a positive impact to the company to
the society and in the country at large
thank you everyone
[Music]